No one is what they seem.
Stonehearst Asylum is a thriller, mystery, horror
film directed by Brad Anderson.
An Oxford Medical School graduate takes a position at a mental institution and soon becomes obsessed with
a female mental patient, but he has no idea of a recent and horrifying staffing change.
Eliza Graves, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Edward Newgate, played by Jim Sturgess.
Mickey Finn, played by David Thewlis.
The Alienist, played by Brendan Gleeson.
Silas Lamb, played by Ben Kingsley.
Dr. Benjamin Salt, played by Michael Caine.
Stonehearst Asylum, previously known as Eliza Graves, is an American psychological
horror film directed by Brad Anderson and written by Joseph Gangemi.
It is loosely based on the 1845 short story "The System of Doctor
Tarr and Professor Fether" by Edgar Allan Poe.
The film, starring Kate Beckinsale, Jim Sturgess, Michael Caine, Ben
Kingsley, and David Thewlis, was released on October 24, 2014.
The film explores themes of mental institution, psychological
thriller, doctor, mental patient, based on short story.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.